

# AHMED **SAMY**Junior DevOps Engineer

☑ asamy0037@gmail.com

Ahmed Maher st, Mansoura, Egypt

+201007591795

## SOCIAL

Ahmedsamymahrous

**in** ahmedsamymahrous

## PROFILE

The nature of my academic studies along with the work experience I have gained and the extracurricular activities wherein I have participated have shaped the person I am today. Having acquired extensive business knowledge... Now, I'm a trainee in ITI (cloud platform development track) to start my way to be a DevOps engineer with a solid business background.

## EDUCATION

ITI - Smart Village

Cloud Platform Development 2020 - 2021

Mansoura University

Faculty of commerce 2015 - 2019

## SKILLS

- Public Speaking
- Problem Solving
- Leadership

## EXPERIENCE

# Ground Handling Agent

Link Aero - Cairo Airport | Feb 2020 - Sep 2020

Handle the commercial, private and military aircraft, and coordinate activities during the ground time to provide fast and efficient services.

# Business Developer

Link Cargo | Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

I was maintaining the existing sales pipeline and Take a lead role in the development of proposals and presentations for new business opportunities and partnerships.

## Customer Service Representative

Xceed (WE - Gold Account) | Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

I was managing and resolve customer complaints, and sell products and place customer orders in the computer system.

## EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

## TEDx

PR Committee Member | 2018 - 2019

I act as a liaison between this NGO and the stakeholders with the purpose of holding successful events.

#### AIESEC

Incoming Global Volunteer | 2017 - 2018

I was bringing in young talent from around the world on long term internships.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

## **Programming Languages**

C / C++ / Python / Java / Bash script / Javascript / SQL

## **Open-source Tools**

Git / Docker / Kubernetes / Jenkins / Ansible / Terraform

## **Cloud Platform**

AWS (Amazon Web Services)

### **Environments**

Linux (Ubuntu / CentOS), Windows

#### Others

Red Hat System Administration / Microservices Architecture / Agile

#### INTERESTS









